# NEIL CREVELING

153 Garfield Place, Apt 3R Brooklyn, NY 11215 585-478-8852 neil.creveling@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/ neilcreveling

LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/neilcreveling-9007a7131/

Portfolio: <a href="https://">https://</a>
neilcreveling.github.io/
Updated-Portfolio/

### SKILLS

- Programming Languages and Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js
- Languages: Native English,
   Proficient French,
   Intermediate Japanese.
- Other Programs: Microsoft Office, Adobe Creative Suite, Raiser's Edge, POS, misc. database software.

# **REFERENCES**

- Available upon request.

# **ABOUT ME**

My name is Neil Creveling, and I am a full stack web developer. Outside of web development, I have a background in fine arts, design, art history, East Asian studies, and I have experience working within non-profits and cultural institutions.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full-time Sales Associate, MUJI U.S.A. Limited

New York, NY — November 2018 - December 2020

Providing and directing excellent customer; cross-selling products to increase purchase amounts; implementing merchandising strategies to increase store sales.

# Library and Archives Volunteer, American Museum of Natural History

New York, NY — February 2019 - present

Inventory unprocessed archival collections; research museum subjects for finding aid biographies; transcribe handwritten field notes for Biodiversity Heritage Library.

#### Studio Intern, Have Art: Will Travel! Inc. and Linda Stein Inc.

New York, NY — Summer 2017

Catalogued artist's oeuvre in FileMaker database; handled, photographed, and stored artworks within a studio setting.

## Development and Gallery Intern, Japan Society

New York, NY — Winter 2015 - Summer 2016

Processed high-level gift renewals; fulfilled membership benefits; researched developing exhibition narratives; created and verified exhibition documentation; assisted with outreach for special exhibitions.

### **EDUCATION**

# VISITING GRADUATE, SCHOOL OF PROFESSIONAL STUDIES — NON-DEGREE Columbia University — 2017-2019

Coursework in Japanese Language; Kyoto Consortium for Japanese Studies, Study Abroad Intensive Language Program, Summer 2018.

# MASTER OF ARTS

Bard Graduate Center — 2016-2018

History of Design, Decorative Arts, and Material Culture.

#### **BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS**

Pratt Institute — 2011-2015

History of Art, Design, and Architecture, minor in Philosophy.